In my room, I hear you call my name
Your perfume inside my pillowcase
I feel you and your fingers trace
But I know you haven't been here in days
I have a video that I watch in my bed
It replays in my head
You say you love me, We, we lay together every night
You touch me, I, I, I'm losin' track of time
You kiss me, I, I, I look into your eyes
But it's only in my mind
Honestly, I only think of you, see your face
Alone in a crowded room, hallucinate
That is the one where you lay, but I know
You haven't been here in days
I have a video that I watch in my bed
It replays in my head
You say you love me, We, we lay together every night
You touch me, I, I, I'm losin' track of time
You kiss me, I, I, I look into your eyes
But it's only in my mind
You say you love me, We, we lay together every night
You touch me, I, I, I'm losing track of time
You kiss me, I, I, I look into your eyes
But it's only in my mind