[Music]
in my room I hear you call my name your
perfume inside my pillow case I feel you
and your fingers Trace but I know you
haven't been here in days I have a video
that I watch in my bed every place in my
head yeah yeah you say you love me we we
like together night you touch me I'm
looseing track of time you kiss me I
look into your eye but it's in my mind
but it's in my mind but it's in
my in
my in my I only think of you see your
face alone in a crowed room L that is
the one why you la but I know you
haven't been here in days I have a video
that I watch in my bed it repls in my he
yeah you say you love me we we like
together every night you touch me I lose
your track of time you kiss me I look
into your eyes but it's only in my mind
but it's h in
my is high in my mind is high in my
mind high in my
[Music]
mind but it's in
my you say you love me we we love
together every night you touch me I Los
a track of time you kiss me I look to
your eyes but it's only in my
life in
my in my
mind high in
my high in my
mind high in my
my but it's in my
[Music]
my