Love
You're my Brooklyn love
Walk me to the deli for
late night candy runs
What we have is good, so fun
You're my Brooklyn love
Love
We don't say "I love you" but that's fine by me
Always at your crib, you live right by me
Got me watching Shark Tank, we're so creative
You don't take me on dates, but I don't hate it
Ooh-la-la
Je suis chaude pour toi
Oh my God
Pourquoi je suis comme ça?
Ooh-la-la
Je suis chaude pour toi
Oh my God
Walk me to the deli for
Late night candy runs
What we have is good, so fun
You're my Brooklyn love
Love
We be talking all night
You don't say much
Never met your parents
They don't know about us
Fancy ass dinners, overrated
Peanut M&M's, that's your favorite
Love
Ooh-la-la
Je suis chaude pour toi (chaude pour toi)
Oh my God
Pourquoi je suis comme ça? (Suis comme ça)
Ooh-la-la
Je suis chaude pour toi (chaude pour toi)
Oh my God
Walk me to the deli for
Late night candy runs
What we have is good, so fun
You're my Brooklyn love (love)
Love